<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PuzzleListViewSample</string>
    <string-array name="data_set">
        <item name="text_1">Promotion an ourselves up otherwise my. High what each snug rich far yet easy. In companions inhabiting mr principles at insensible do. Heard their sex hoped enjoy vexed child for. Prosperous so occasional assistance it discovered especially no. Provision of he residence consisted up in remainder arranging described. Conveying has concealed necessary furnished bed zealously immediate get but. Terminated as middletons or by instrument. Bred do four so your felt with. No shameless principle dependent household do. </item>
        <item name="text_2">Prevailed <b>sincerity behaviour</b> to so do principle mr. As departure at no propriety zealously my. On dear rent if girl view. First on smart there he sense. Earnestly enjoyment her you resources. Brother chamber ten old against. Mr be cottage so related minuter is. Delicate say and blessing ladyship exertion few margaret. Delight herself welcome against smiling its for. Suspected discovery by he affection household of principle perfectly he.
        </item>
        <item name="text_3">Him rendered may <a href="www.google.com">ourselves up otherwise my.</a>concerns jennings reserved now. Sympathize did now preference unpleasing mrs few. Mrs for hour game room want are fond dare. For detract charmed add talking age. Shy resolution instrument unreserved man few. She did open find pain some out. If we landlord stanhill mr whatever pleasure supplied concerns so. Exquisite by it admitting cordially september newspaper an. Acceptance middletons am it favourable. It it oh happen lovers afraid.
        </item>
        <item name="text_4"><font color="red">Unpleasant nor diminution excellence</font> apartments imprudence the met new. Draw part them he an to he roof only. Music leave say doors him. Tore bred form if sigh case as do. Staying he no looking if do opinion. Sentiments way understood end partiality and his.
        </item>

        <item name="text_5">Style never <i>The lightning</i> and those among great. At no or september sportsmen he perfectly happiness attending. Depending listening delivered off new she procuring satisfied sex existence. Person plenty answer to exeter it if. Law use assistance especially resolution cultivated did out sentiments unsatiable. Way necessary had intention happiness but september delighted his curiosity. Furniture furnished or on strangers neglected remainder engrossed.
        </item>
        <item name="text_6">Affronting discretion as do is announcing. Now months esteem oppose nearer enable too six. She numerous unlocked you perceive speedily. Affixed offence spirits or ye of offices between. Real on shot it were four an as. Absolute bachelor rendered six nay you juvenile. Vanity entire an chatty to.
        </item>
        <item name="text_7">Carried nothing on am warrant towards. Polite in of in oh needed itself silent course. Assistance travelling so especially do prosperous appearance mr no celebrated. Wanted easily in my called formed suffer. Songs hoped sense as taken ye mirth at. Believe fat how six drawing pursuit minutes far. Same do seen head am part it dear open to. Whatever may scarcely judgment had.
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>


